Guide to the Records of the Program in Archival Management 1978-1994 RG 20.3
New York University Archives
Records of the Program in Archival Management
1978-1994
RG 20.3
New York University Archives
13.0 linear feet 13 linear feet
This collection consists of the records of the Archives Program in the History Department from 1978-1994. There are administrative communications, class syllabi, articles, student surveys, and student records.
New York University. Dept. of History.
Scope and Content Note
The documents in this collection reflect the students, faculty and curricula that have comprised the Archives Program. The collection also illuminates the connections between archives students and the profession as a whole, through internship programs and affiliation with professional organizations.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Archives Program was founded in 1977 as a training program for archivists, historical editors, administrators, and manuscript curators. Administratively, the program is part of the History Department in the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences; most of the faculty that teach in the Program reside in this Department. The program culminates in a New York State Board of Regents Certificate in Archives, Historical Society Administration, and Historical Editing. Students may also choose to pursue jointly an M.A. or Ph.D. in History or a related field.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
Contact the University Archives for specific access restrictions. This includes all materials in boxes 6-9 and 13.
This collection is in
off-site storage
.
Margaret Sanger Papers Project.; New York University. Dept. of History.; New York University. Graduate School of Arts and Science.; Society of American Archivists.; Articles.; Correspondence.; Papers and lectures.; surveys (documents)
- Series I: Materials
  - Central Zionist Office: Berlin, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227158 8
  - Archives Survey, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Program Summary, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Archives Grads Survey, Fall, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation Visits, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Archives Certificate Requirements, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Certificate Requirements, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - SAA Education Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Archival Certification-SAA Notes, Proposals, Correspondence, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Program Information-Other NYU Programs, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - SAA Education Committee & Educations, Roundtables, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - SAA Education Committee, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Archives Grad Survey, October, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Assistant Guidelines, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Administrative History and Records Management, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Administrative History/Records Management (G. Smith, Lecturer), 0000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Archives Brochure, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Archives Program, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - G57.2010 Spring 1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - G57.2010 Field Report Assignment, Spring, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - .2010 Syllabus, Spring, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Archives, Historical Societies and the Interpretation of American Urban Culture, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Teaching Appraisal #2, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Intro. To Computers, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Problems in Archives Kits (SAA), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Practicum, Spring, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Legal and Ethical Issues, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Computer Use-RUN, 0000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Practicum Class, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Readings .1010, Fall, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227159 6
  - Photo Exercise, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Management of Archives, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Laurence E. Steadman, "Telephone Accounting, 1877-1912", 0000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Workshop, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Practicum, Spring, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - NHPRC Conference, April 16-17, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Informaco Information, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Conservation and Micrographics, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Historian and the Visual Record, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Consumer Management Archives, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank Archives-Linda E., 0000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Citibank, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Col. Pomrenze, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - N.Y. County Clerks Office, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Electronic Music Center, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Envirosphere, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn Historical Society, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Brooklyn Rediscovery, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Business Archives, NYU Correspondence…information, etc, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Cadwalader, Wickersham, & Taft, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Carnegie Hall Archives, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Camp Shanks Historical Project, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - NY Chamber of Commerce, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Ron Grete-Columbia Oral History, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Chase Manhattan Intern, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Muller Intro, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence-Archivists, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence With Students Not Now Enrolled, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - History of Advertising Archives, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - ACLU Archives, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - American Craft Council Library, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - American Musical Theatre Archives, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - American Sound Archives, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Astoria Motion Picture and TV Foundation, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - .2010 Carol Bellamy Project, Spring, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Bellevue Hospital Project, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence With Archivists, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence-Archivists, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Fran Blouin, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Archives Faculty-C.U.'s, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Photos A-H, Fall, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Museum Studies Packet, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Advanced Seminar in Archival Management, G57.3009, Spring, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Advanced Seminar in Archival Management, Syllabus, Spring, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Robert Warner Lecture at NYU, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Museum Studies, May, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Museum Studies, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Photos Inc., Miller Report & Archives, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Margaret Sanger Project, Historical Editing, G57.2009, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227160 4
  - Media & History, B. Abrash, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Public History, Women's History Program, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Computers & Archival Administration, Syllabus, Orig. Fall, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Computers & Archives, G57.2017, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - G57.2017, Computers & Archival Administration, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Computers & Archives, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Conservation and Micrographics, Spring, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Historical Archaeology, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - British Archives, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Material Dorfman's Readings, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Historical Journal Editing, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Oral History, Fall, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Advanced Internship, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Reading-Research in Archival Management, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Community & Local History, G57.1752, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - AASLH-SAA-Publications, Archive Association Membership, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Archivists, SAA Panel Etc., 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Archivists' Roundtable, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reagan Cutbacks-Letters, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - AASLH-Certification, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - SAA, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - American Archivist, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fran Blouin Grant, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Slide Show Material, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - NARS Co-op Program, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - SAA Sections: College & University Acquisitions, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - NHPRC Fellowship Program, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Midwest Archives Conference, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Archival Supplies, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - ACT Newsletter, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - AA Steering Committee, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Roundtable, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Swarthmore Peace Collection, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Town Hall Records, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Vietnam War Archives, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Robert Wagner, Sr. Labor Archives, Tamiment Library, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Yale-China Photo Archives Project, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - New York Stock Exchange Archives, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Stock Exchange Archives, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - New School for Social Research Archives, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - PEA-Public Education Association, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Hassadah Archives, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227161 2
  - IAS Grant Proposal, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Inc., 0000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ITT Records Management, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Louisa Bowen-Research in History-Archives, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fales Collections-Bobst NYU Archives Design, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Federal Records Center-Bayonne, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Franklin Furnace, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - LaGuardia Archives, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cornell (Cornwell?) Archives, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Envirosphere Co., 0000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Civil Defence Editorial, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Exams-Sample, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Archives Week, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Archives Program, December, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Archives Exams, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - SAA Certification, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - American Field Service, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Israel, May-June, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Archival Theory Panel, October, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Archival Education: Readings, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - NEH Correspondence, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - New School-Records Survey Exercise, Spring, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Advanced Internship, Fall, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Practicum: Student Evaluations, Spring, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Intro. Course, Fall, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Field Reports, Spring, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Robert College, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Religious Archives Service Agency, Tom Wilsted, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Paul Robeson Archives, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Birthplace, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Sephardic Archives (Brooklyn), 0000 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Social Science Research Concil, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Shubert Archives-School of the Arts, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - New-York Historical Society, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - New York Philharmonic Archives, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - New York State Archives, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - New York Public Library Manuscripts Division, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - NYU Archives-Notes, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Puerto Rican Records Survey, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Municipal Archives & Records Service, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - L.A. Police Files: RFK Murder, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - John Mason, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Met Life, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Metropolitan Opera Archives, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Mobil Oil Corp., 0000 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Pierpont Morgan Library, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Municipal Archives, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - National Congress on Historical Docs., 0000 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - New School-Archives Proposal, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - NJUMD-Stuart Sammie, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - N.Y. Historical Resources Center, MSS Survey, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Untitled Folder (Field Reports?), 0000 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Field Reports on Archives, Fall, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Magazines and Catalogs, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence With Archivists, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227162 0
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Field Trip, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Field Reports, A-M, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Archival Practicum-El Kind, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - The Connecticut Historical Society-Koss, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Attachment B, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NYC Dept. of Records and Information Services Annual Reports, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Grumman History Center-Sniffin, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Index to Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Field Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bx. Botanical Garden, Bx. Zoological Society-Internship Material, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Field Reports Completed, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Case Western Reserve/Akron Trip, August, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - SSRC Proposal, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - University of Wisconsin-Trip and Information, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - University of Maryland Program, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - University of Illinois Program, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - June Trip to Midwest and MARAC, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, Research Resources Program, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Wisconsin and Wayne State Programs and Report, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Wisconsin Univ. and Maryland Univ. Reports, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Wayne State and Ohio Historical Student Materials, 0000 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227163 8
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, 0000 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227165 3
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Student Files, H-S, 1977-1992, 0000 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227166 1
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Student Files, S-Z, 1977-1989, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Needs to be Filed…Students, 0000 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Thellen, David: "Memory & American History", 0000 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Thibodeau, Sharon Gibbs: "Archival Arrangement & Description", 0000 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Sussman, Warren: "History & The American Intellectual: The Uses of a Usable Past", 0000 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Swanson, Dorothy: "Tamiment Wagner Labor Archives", 0000 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Storm-Clark, Christopher: "The Miners': 1870-1970: A Test", 0000 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Steward, Virginia: "Problems of Confidentiality in the Administration of Personal Case Records", 0000 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Stewart, V. & Ritzenthaler, M.: "Constituencies of Urban Archives: Donors, Users, and Institutions", 0000 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Spring, Joel: "Mass Culture & School Sports", 0000 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Student Records, 0000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227167 9
  - Student Records, 0000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Student Records, 0000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Student Records, 0000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Student Records, 0000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Student Records, 0000 (Box 9, Folder 6)